Finding Aid for the Albert McCleery Papers PASC.0098
UCLA Library Special Collections
Albert McCleery papers
1935-1971
UCLA Library Special Collections
McCleery, Albert
PASC.0098
35.0 Linear Feet (83 boxes)
Producer and director Albert McCleery is best remembered for his theatre-in-the-round productions of television classics including Cameo Theater, Fireside Theatre, Hallmark Hall of Fame, and NBC Matinee Theatre. The collection consists primarily of television, and some radio scripts, along with production material, correspondence, and profession-related subject files. Among the projects represented are Cameo Theatre, CBS Television Workshop, Hallmark Hall of Fame, and NBC Matinee Theatre.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Mrs. Sue McCleery, 1980.
UCLA Catalog Record ID:
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9922213593606533
Biography
Albert McCleery was born December 30, 1911 in Lawrence, Kentucky. He was a contract writer for Columbia Pictures (1940-41) and director of Fordham University Theatre (1949). McCleery is best remembered for his theatre-in-the-round productions of classics for television including Cameo Theater, Fireside Theatre, Hallmark Hall of Fame, and Matinee Theatre. He was also staff director in the NBC Television Programming Department (1949) and went on to become senior executive producer and director of Cameo Theatre. McCleery produced and directed for Hallmark Hall of Fame, devised NBC's Matinee Theater (1955), joined CBS (1959), and became producer of the CBS workshop. He died on May 13, 1972.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of material related to the career of producer and director, Albert McCleery. Primarily includes television scripts and some radio scripts along with production material, correspondence, and profession-related files that include resumes and photographs. Popular television roductions represented in the collection include Cameo Theatre (May-August 1950, January-March 1952, July-August 1955), CBS Television Workshop (January-December 1960), Fireside Theatre (June-October 1951), Hallmark Hall of Fame (July 1952-June 1955), The Kate Smith Hour (September 1951-June 1952), NBC's Matinee Theatre (October 1955-June 1958), and Your Prize Story (1952) among others. Radio scripts document the program Inheritance (April-September 1954). Also included are a small amount of personal files, materials representing unproduced projects, conferences and speaking engagements, and a small number of theatre-related files.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Television Projects
Radio Projects
Unproduced Projects
Correspondence
Professional Subject Files
Network Files
Theater Files
Conferences and Speaking Engagements
Personal Files
Related Material
Sidney Carroll Papers (Collection 94). UCLA Library Special Collections.
Hallmark Hall of Fame Scripts and Production Material (Collection 71). UCLA Library Special Collections, UCLA.
Collection of Scripts and Production Material for the Television Series NBC Matinee Theatre (Collection 1038). UCLA Library Special Collections.
Collection of Scripts for the Television Series The Further Adventures of Ellery Queen (Collection 1039). UCLA Special Collections, UCLA.
Television producers and directors -- Archives.; McCleery, Albert -- Archives
- Television Projects, 1950-1960; (1-3, 5, 7, 8, 10-20, 22)
  Scope and Content
  The Television Projects Series consists of material documenting McCleery's contributions to popular American television programing during the 1950s. Productions represented include Cameo Theatre, CBS Television Workshop, Fireside Theatre, Hallmark Hall of Fame, The Kate Smith Hour, NBC's Matinee Theatre, and Your Prize Story among others. The series is arranged alphabetically by program titles.
  - Title Clearances
    - Title Clearances for McCleery shows (15 items), 1959, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      General note
      MANHATTAN, NEW YORK, 21, NEW YORK, and CBS THRESHOLD, among
  - BOBBY CLARK SHOW (THE)
    - Would Be Gentleman (5 items), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      Individual program routine, running order, closing crawl, and production breakdown.
  - CAMEO THEATRE
    - Budget information for the series sponsorsed by Hallmark (17 items), 1952 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Foote, Cone and Belding Advertising - correspondence (3 items), 1955 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Form letters used to answer viewer mail (3 items), no date (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Lists and comments for television adaptation (10 items), 1962 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Photographs illustrating Cameo style (32 items), no date (Box 18, Folder 4)
      Assumed to be from CAMEO THEATRE.
    - Photographs illustrating Cameo style (47 items), no date (Box 18, Folder 3)
      Assumed to be from CAMEO THEATRE. Possibly representing Murder is a Matter of Opinion and Weep for the Heart.
    - Photographs illustrating the Cameo style (24 items), no date (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Photographs illustrating the Cameo style (Approximately 42 items), no date (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Assumed to be from CAMEO THEATRE. Possibly representing A Daughter to Think About
    - Production information (51 items), 1951- 1953 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Production budgets: staff, set, scripts, shooting and construction; and sponsor changes.
    - Promotional and advertising brochures and newspaper clipping (3 items), 1951 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Avalanche, 7/9/1951 (Box 81)
    - Betrayal, 7/2/1951 (Box 81)
    - Blackout, 6/25/1951 (Box 81)
    - Breaking of the Bough, 7/17/1955 (Box 80)
    - CAMEO THEATRE and four other programs Nielsen ratings (5 items), no date (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Cannon's Curtains, 7/19/1950 (Box 83)
    - Canon's Curtains (The), 3/16/1952 (Box 80)
    - Clinic (The), 7/12/1950 (Box 83)
    - Company, 8/7/1955 (Box 80)
    - Complaint from viewer re. McCleery as recipient of the William I Kaufman Award (3 items), 1952 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Dark of the Moon, 1/6/1952 (Box 80)
    - Debut, 3/30/1952 (Box 80)
    - Deception, 7/16/1951 (Box 81)
    - Gathering Twilight (The), 1/13/1952 (Box 80)
    - Googan, 8/2/1950 (Box 83)
    - Grown Ones (The), 7/24/1955 (Box 80)
    - Heart's Choice, 8/27/1951 (Box 81)
    - Hutch, 7/31/1955 (Box 80)
    - Inca of Perusalem (The), 7/3/1955 (Box 80)
    - It Takes a Thief, 5/16/1950 (Box 83)
    - Legend of Liz, 4/6/1952 (Box 80)
    - Line of Duty (The), 7/26/1950 (Box 83)
    - Long Walk (The), 5/30/1950 (Box 83)
    - Long Walk (The) - fan mail (40 items), 1950 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Lottery (The), 6/14/1950 (Box 83)
    - Lottery (The) - magazine clippings (7 items), 1951 July - November (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Review and interview with McCleery, McCleery on theater in the round.
    - Man from the South (The), 8/14/1955 (Box 80)
    - Man Who Played Lincoln (The), 2/10/1952 (Box 80)
    - Manhattan Footsteps, 6/7/1950 (Box 83)
    - Of Unsound Mind, 7/23/1951 (Box 81)
    - Paper Sack (The), 9/20/1950 (Box 83)
    - Paper Sack (The), 1/27/1952 (Box 80)
    - Point of View (A), 8/16/1950 (Box 83)
    - Problem Child, 2/3/1952 (Box 80)
    - Richard III, 7/30/1950 (Box 83)
    - Ringside Seat, 8/30/1950 (Box 83)
    - Saralee and the Children, 8/23/1950 (Box 83)
    - Special Delivery, 6/18/1951 (Box 81)
    - Strange Identity, 8/6/1951 (Box 81)
    - Third Time (The), 7/30/1951 (Box 81)
    - Thompsons (The), 2/17/1952 (Box 80)
    - Treasure Trove, 4/13/1952 (Box 80)
    - Triumph of Justice, 8/9/1950 (Box 83)
    - Visit (The), 1/20/1952 (Box 80)
    - Weep for the Heart, 6/21/1950 (Box 83)
    - Whisper of a Witness, 7/10/1955 (Box 80)
    - Young is the Heart, 3/23/1952 (Box 80)
  - CBS TELEVISION WORKSHOP
    - Advertising report with figures for television stations, newspapers and TV GUIDE, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Biographies of writers involved with the series, resumes of two directors ( 9 items), 1961 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and budgets concerning music and composers to be used in the series (28 items), 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Directors Workshop - letters of appreciation to participants (approximately 50 items), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Directors Workshop - letters of appreciation to participants (15 items), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Form letters in reply to script submissions during hiatus of series (19 items), 1961 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Interoffice correspondence concerning budgets, effects, overtime and other production related concerns (20 items), 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Letters protesting series' cancellation (6 items), 1960, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Proposal for the series' second season, no date (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Afterthought, 5/8/1960 (Box 65)
    - Another Valley, 9/16/1960 (Box 65)
    - Anton Waldek (II), 4/3/1960 (Box 64)
    - Bible Salesman (The), 4/10/1960 (Box 64)
    - Brick and the Rose (The), 1/24/1960 (Box 64)
    - Brown Girl, Brownstones, 4/24/1960 (Box 65)
    - CBS-THRESHOLD (later changed to CBS TELEVISION WORKSHOP) proposal and budgets for proposed formats (8 items), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Chances of Sybele Dobb (The), 10/16/1960 (Box 65)
    - Christmas Song, 12/25/1960 (Box 66)
    - Cry of a Summer Night, no date (Box 66)
    - Dirtiest Word in the English Lang, 10/2/1960 (Box 65)
    - Flight of Fancy, 12/4/1960 (Box 66)
    - Friday Dinner on Middle Neck Road, 2/28/1960 (Box 64)
    - Furnished Room, 3/27/1960 (Box 64)
    - Head of a King, 1/31/1960 (Box 64)
    - How to Shoot Fish in a Barrel, 10/23/1960 (Box 65)
    - Lady of the Dawn, 3/6/1960 (Box 64)
    - Limbo Kid (The), 2/7/1960 (Box 64)
    - Mandy, 5/1/1960 (Box 65)
    - Mind's Eye (The), 12/11/1960 (Box 66)
    - Mortgaged Heart (The), 11/13/1960 (Box 65)
    - My Theory About Girls, 11/27/1960 (Box 66)
    - Newpaper clipping with background on the show, no date (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Pattern of Words and Music (A), 11/20/1960 (Box 66)
    - Seven Who Were Hanged (The) - script, no date (Box 19, Folder 7)
      Appears to for the CBS TELEVISION WORKSHOP
    - Song of Louise in the Morning (The), 3/13/1960 (Box 64)
    - Tessie Malfitano (I), 4/3/1960 (Box 64)
    - Tobias and the Angel, 4/17/1960 (Box 64)
    - Walls Between (The), 2/14/1960 (Box 64)
    - Radio Projects
      - INHERITANCE, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 3)
        Correspondence and interoffice communication on budget, scripts, and other inquiries (30 items)
      - INHERITANCE, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 2)
        Ideas and treatments for episodes (2 items)
      - INHERITANCE, 6/6/1954 (Box 82)
        But for the Courage of a Woman
      - INHERITANCE, 8/28/1954 (Box 82)
        Charter Oak, The
      - INHERITANCE, 4/11/1954 (Box 82)
        Dorothea Lynde Dix
      - INHERITANCE, 8/15/1954 (Box 82)
        Flag That Talks, The
      - INHERITANCE, 5/16/1954 (Box 82)
        Flight to Nowhere
      - INHERITANCE, 4/25/1954 (Box 82)
        Giant of Virginia, The
      - INHERITANCE, 9/19/1954 (Box 82)
        Gibraltar of the Hudson, The
      - INHERITANCE, 5/2/1954 (Box 82)
        In Whatsoever House I Enter
      - INHERITANCE, 5/30/1954 (Box 82)
        Lewis and Clark Expedition, The
      - INHERITANCE, 4/18/1954 (Box 82)
        Mountain Men, The
      - INHERITANCE, 5/23/1954 (Box 82)
        Nutmegger and the Turtle, The
      - INHERITANCE, 9/4/1954 (Box 82)
        One Mile of Rock
      - INHERITANCE, 7/4/1954 (Box 82)
        Proclaim Liberty
      - INHERITANCE, 8/1/1954 (Box 82)
        Rails to the Pacific
      - INHERITANCE, 4/4/1954 (Box 82)
        Time of Decision
      - INHERITANCE, 5/9/1954 (Box 82)
        To Save a City
      - INHERITANCE, 7/18/1954 (Box 82)
        Victory on Lake Erie
      - INHERITANCE, 6/20/1954 (Box 82)
        Whipple's War
      - INHERITANCE, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 1)
        Program budget and list of actors (2 items)
  - FIRESIDE THEATRE
    - Agnew Jones and the Giants, 8/8/1951 (Box 81)
    - Deliver Us from Evil, 7/31/1951 (Box 81)
    - Little Night Music (The), 7/17/1951 (Box 81)
    - Lottery (The), 6/29/1951 (Box 81)
    - Make-Believe, 6/22/1951 (Box 81)
    - Moment of Glory, 7/3/1951 (Box 81)
    - Vigil (The), 7/10/1951 (Box 81)
  - HALLMARK HALL OF FAME
    - Budget for series, including weekly budget reports (41 items), 1952 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Commercial timings for episode dated Oct. 1, 1953 and Feb. 2 to June 28, 1955 episodes. 22 items., 1953 Oct 1 and 1955 Feb-June (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence concerning production team's relocation to Hollywood (4 items), 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Fan mail for episode "Richard II" (6 items), 1954 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Fan mail, suggestions, job requests correspondence (21 items), 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Hallmark Cards' Kansas City office - correspondence from (8 items), 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - HALLMARK HALL OF FAME radio and television advertising policies (1 item), 1955 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Interdepartment and interoffice correspondence (77 items), 1953-1955 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Legal correspondence concerning copyright lawsuit over the use of series' name (6 items), 1953 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Lists of available actors (by talent agency) (4 items), 1955 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Nielsen ratings, properties held by Hallmark and prospective air dates for some episodes (9 items), 1952-1954 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      Nielsen ratings for Hallmark and Cameo shows.
    - Photograph by Brady, 3/22/1953 (Box 79)
    - Synopses of stories under consideration for half-hour episodes (58 items), 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Synopses of stories under consideration for one hour episodes (14 items), [1952-1953?] (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Accused (The), 3/1/1953 (Box 79)
    - Adventures of Lt Contee (The), 3/6/1955 (Box 74)
    - Aesop and Rhodope, 12/13/1953 (Box 71)
    - Aimee De Rivery, Mother of Sultans, 4/24/1955 (Box 74)
    - Armour-Bearer (The), 5/30/1954 (Box 72)
    - Blaze of Darkness, 12/27/1953 (Box 77)
    - Cadet Poe, 6/12/1955 (Box 73)
    - Choirmaster of Leipzig (The), 10/10/1954 (Box 72)
    - Clay of Kings (The), 6/7/1953 (Box 78)
    - Come to the Window, 6/13/1954 (Box 72)
    - Courtship of Miles Standish (The), 11/22/1953 (Box 71)
    - Crabapple Saint, 8/24/1952 (Box 75)
    - Cradle Song, 5/8/1955 (Box 74)
    - Crazy Betty (The) Story of Christine Granville and Henry Ford treatments (appears to be from HALLMARK) (3 items), no date (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Crown of Wings, 2/15/1953 (Box 79)
    - Crusade to Liberty, 12/6/1953 (Box 77)
    - Crusader against Cruelty, 2/14/1954 (Box 77)
    - Dark of Moon - correspondence (3 items), 1955 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Deadlock, 12/5/1954 (Box 73)
    - Dinner for the General, 2/22/1953 (Box 79)
    - Do Not Cry for Me, 9/12/1954 (Box 72)
    - Dynamite, 9/5/1954 (Box 72)
    - Fanny Stevenson, 1/4/1953 (Box 79)
    - Farmer from Monticello, 6/26/1955 (Box 73)
    - Father Time, 12/28/1952 (Box 79)
    - Father Who Had No Sons (The), 6/19/1955 (Box 73)
    - Finest Gift (The), 3/27/1955 (Box 74)
    - Flight from Cathay, 6/20/1954 (Box 72)
    - Four stages in the creation of a publicity pamphlet (3 items), 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - General's Bible (The), 1/18/1953 (Box 79)
    - Giant on Wheels, 1/30/1955 (Box 74)
    - Good Samaritan (The), 3/7/1954 (Box 76)
    - Green Mountain Boys (The), 4/3/1955 (Box 74)
    - Hamlet - review (1 item), 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Hands of Clara Schumann (The), 2/7/1954 (Box 77)
    - Harp of Erin (The), 3/15/1953 (Box 79)
    - Hills Are Green (The), 12/14/1952 (Box 79)
    - Horace Mann's Miracle, 3/8/1953 (Box 79)
    - Hucklebery Finn - correspondence and budget (8 items), 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Imaginary Invalid (The), 11/1/1953 (Box 71)
    - Immortal Oath (The), 10/10/1954 (Box 72)
    - Joan of Arc, 12/7/1952 (Box 79)
    - John Paul Jones, 7/4/1954 (Box 72)
    - Joyful Tydings (The), 12/26/1954 (Box 73)
    - King Richard II, 1/24/1954 (Box 77)
    - Label of Truth (The), 1/23/1955 (Box 74)
    - Lady in the Wings (The), 10/24/1954 (Box 73)
    - Lady of Liberty (The), 5/10/1953 (Box 78)
    - Lafayette for Freedom!, 4/25/1954 (Box 76)
    - Last Voyage (The), 11/29/1953 (Box 71)
    - Liberator (The), 4/11/1954 (Box 76)
    - Lincoln's Little Correspondent, 2/8/1953 (Box 79)
    - Lone Star (The), 1/31/1954 (Box 77)
    - Lonely Path (The), 11/8/1953 (Box 71)
    - Lydia, 4/10/1955 (Box 74)
    - Man against Pain, 6/21/1953 (Box 78)
    - Man of Many Ideas (A), 9/19/1954 (Box 72)
    - Man Who Tore Down the Wall (The), 4/17/1955 (Box 74)
    - Man with a Camera (The), 5/22/1955 (Box 74)
    - Matter of Principle (A), 11/14/1954 (Box 73)
    - McCoy of Abiline, 10/18/1953 (Box 71)
    - Mercer Girls (The), 6/28/1953 (Box 78)
    - Miss Tracy of Mt Vernon, 2/21/1954 (Box 77)
    - Moby Dick, 5/16/1954 (Box 72)
    - Never Kick a Man Upstairs, 10/25/1953 (Box 71)
    - No Man is an Island, 5/3/1953 (Box 78)
    - Of Time and the River, 8/4/1952 (Box 71)
    - Ordeal of Thomas Jefferson (The), 3/28/1954 (Box 76)
    - Other Wise Man (The), 4/5/1953 (Box 78)
    - Out of Jules Verne, 3/21/1954 (Box 76)
    - Path to Peace (The), 10/31/1954 (Box 73)
    - Patrick Henry of Virginia, 2/6/1955 (Box 74)
    - Petticoat Revolution, 5/2/1954 (Box 76)
    - Pine Tree Shilling (The), 1/9/1955 (Box 73)
    - Pirate and the Lawyer (The), 3/13/1955 (Box 74)
    - Portrait by Whistler, 5/9/1954 (Box 76)
    - President for a Day, 11/21/1954 (Box 73)
    - Promise (The), 5/15/1955 (Box 74)
    - Proudly I Love, 5/24/1953 (Box 78)
    - Province of Man (The), 12/12/1954 (Box 73)
    - Queen is Born (A), 3/29/1953 (Box 78)
    - Queen's Way (A), 10/11/1953 (Box 71)
    - Reckless Youth (A), 6/6/1954 (Box 72)
    - Reluctant Redeemer (The), 9/26/1954 (Box 72)
    - Road to Tara (The), 3/14/1954 (Box 76)
    - Scale of Justice, 1/3/1954 (Box 77)
    - Scott's Castle, 6/14/1953 (Box 78)
    - Serra and San Francisco, 5/23/1954 (Box 72)
    - Shining Beacon (The), 2/13/1955 (Box 74)
    - Siege (The), 11/7/1954 (Box 73)
    - Skipper of the Skies, 4/12/1953 (Box 78)
    - Small One (The), 12/21/1952 (Box 79)
    - Smile for Danger (A), 9/27/1953 (Box 71)
    - Smile For Danger (A) - Master Broadcast Report (1 item), 1953 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Smile For Danger (A) - scene by scene property and set breakdowns (1 item), 1953 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Socrates' Wife, 1/25/1953 (Box 79)
    - Soldier of Peace, 5/17/1953 (Box 78)
    - Soldier's Bride, 3/20/1955 (Box 74)
    - Span of Time (A), 1/11/1953 (Box 79)
    - Spark of Genius, 5/31/1953 (Box 78)
    - St Cloud Storm (The), 1/17/1954 (Box 77)
    - Story of Martha Curtis Washington, 2/20/1955 (Box 74)
    - Story of Ruth (The), 2/28/1954 (Box 76)
    - Story of Ruth (The), 4/18/1954 (Box 76)
    - Story of William Tell, 1/2/1955 (Box 73)
    - Talking Wire (The), 2/27/1955 (Box 74)
    - Tempering of the Sword (The), 6/5/1955 (Box 73)
    - To My Valentine, 2/1/1953 (Box 79)
    - Touch of Steel (The), 5/1/1955 (Box 74)
    - Turbulent Air (The), 2/28/1954 (Box 77)
    - Wife unto Caesar, 6/27/1954 (Box 72)
    - World on a Wire (The), 4/19/1953 (Box 78)
    - Yankee Roadblock, 10/17/1954 (Box 72)
    - Young Ben, 1/16/1955 (Box 74)
    - Young William Penn, 4/4/1954 (Box 76)
  - HALLMARK SUMMER THEATRE
    - Carlson Legend (The), 8/3/1952 (Box 75)
    - Dutch Treat, 9/7/1952 (Box 75)
    - I Lift My Lamp, 8/17/1952 (Box 75)
    - Last Command (The), 8/10/1952 (Box 75)
    - Legend of Josiah Blow (The), 7/6/1952 (Box 75)
    - Real Glory (The), 7/13/1952 (Box 75)
    - Refresher Course, 8/31/1952 (Box 75)
    - Salvage, 7/20/1952 (Box 75)
    - Twenty-One Plus, 7/27/1952 (Box 75)
  - HALLMARK THEATRE
    - Bachelor and the Ballot (The), 10/12/1952 (Box 75)
    - Bride's Tea Pot (The), 9/21/1952 (Box 75)
    - Horns of a Dilemma, 9/14/1952 (Box 75)
    - Sometime She's Sunday, 9/28/1952 (Box 75)
  - KATE SMITH DAYTIME HOUR (THE)
    - Rehearsal scene, 3/21/1952 (Box 70)
    - After School, 3/5/1952 (Box 69)
    - And Still Champion, 1/7/1952 (Box 69)
    - Birthday, 4/10/1952 (Box 70)
    - Code of a Gentleman (The), 5/20/1952 (Box 70)
    - Cure (The), 4/22/1952 (Box 70)
    - Detached Duty, 5/16/1952 (Box 70)
    - Dramatic Irony, 1/2/1952 (Box 69)
    - Exclusively Yours, 12/25/1951 (Box 69)
    - Game (The), 11/13/1951 (Box 69)
    - Girl from Venice (The), 2/26/1952 (Box 69)
    - Heart-Line, 4/2/1952 (Box 70)
    - Incident in Paris, 12/6/1951 (Box 69)
    - Lace on Her Petticoat, 9/25/1951 (Box 69)
    - Other Side of Town (The), 3/11/1952 (Box 69)
    - Painting (The), 11/11/1951 (Box 69)
    - Places, Please!, 6/5/1952 (Box 70)
    - Real Caroline Cluett (A), 5/29/1952 (Box 70)
    - Reckoning (The), 4/14/1952 (Box 70)
    - She Walks in Beauty, 5/9/1952 (Box 70)
    - Sold to the Lady, 2/19/1952 (Box 69)
    - Special Edition, 2/5/1952 (Box 69)
    - Spring Meeting, 12/24/1951 (Box 69)
    - Strangers in Passing, 3/28/1952 (Box 70)
    - Subtle Touch (The), 10/23/1951 (Box 69)
    - Such Sweet Sorrow, 10/11/1951 (Box 69)
    - Sure Thing (The), 5/1/1952 (Box 70)
    - To the Victor, 2/15/1952 (Box 69)
    - Truth Shall Make You Free (The), 1/17/1952 (Box 69)
    - Waiting for Andre, 1/31/1952 (Box 69)
  - KATE SMITH EVENING HOUR (THE)
    - After Dinner Story, 1/30/1952 (Box 68)
    - Anne of the Thousand Days, no date (Box 68)
    - Beginner's Luck, 11/21/1951 (Box 68)
    - In the Fog, 10/24/1951 (Box 68)
    - It Takes a Thief, 10/3/1951 (Box 68)
    - Land's End, 1/16/1952 (Box 68)
    - Listen (A)lice, 12/20/1951 (Box 69)
    - Little Boy Who Wouldn't Smile (The), 11/7/1951 (Box 68)
    - Lonely Night for a Birthday (A), 9/26/1951 (Box 68)
    - Midsummer Night's Dream (A), 12/12/1951 (Box 68)
    - Mr Tzicitizen, 2/13/1952 (Box 68)
    - My Luckiest Day, 1/2/1951 (Box 68)
    - Operation--Sunshine, 3/19/1952 (Box 68)
    - Power of the Press, 10/10/1951 (Box 68)
    - Quietest Part of London, 2/27/1952 (Box 68)
    - Reflected Glory, 12/26/1951 (Box 68)
    - Small One (The), 12/19/1951 (Box 68)
    - To Catch a Thief, 1/23/1952 (Box 68)
    - Trio by Lamplight, 11/14/1951 (Box 68)
    - We Ain't Popular, 2/20/1952 (Box 68)
  - KATE SMITH HOUR (THE)
    - Lists of leading actors and writers representing episodes in the series (1 item), no date (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - LUNAR PRODUCTIONS
    - Correspondence to and from Lunar Productions (9 items), 1962 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - LUX THEATRE
    - Browning Version (The) - camera angles, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - MANHATTAN
    - Budgets for music costs, suggestions of possible composers for series score (12 items), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Cast and personnel lists, budget figures, scene and show rundowns and rehearsal schedule (25 items), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence regarding scripts, production and applications (Approx 40 items), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Informal budget for series and "Production and Facilites Estimating Form" (2 items), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Legal clearences for series title and office communication relating to script purchases (18 items), 1959, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Office communication on scripts under consideration and synopses of published stories under consideration (24 items), 1952-1960 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Press release explaining the postponement of premiere (1 item), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Synopses of four stories under consideration (4 items), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Girl at the Wainright Hotel (The) - first and second drafts (4 items), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      With two lists of characters. 1960. 4 items.
    - Girl at the Wainright Hotel (The) (2 items), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      Rehearsal draft and third draft.